Is it really true
To je skutečně pravda
That's no secret
Není to žádné tajemství
What a bastard!
Jaký parchant!
Get up, quickly, we have a problem
Vstávej rychle, máme problém
Seems like Dar was sniffing around here.
Dar tu byl pravděpodobně.
Our packet of weed have vanished
Balík trávy nám zmizel
searching everywhere and can't find it.
Hledám všude i tak ho nemám.
He must've gone to the farm
Musel se vydat na farmu
maybe I'll find the package there.
Myslel, že tam balík najde.
This is my best weed
To je moje nejlepší tráva
and I won't share it with Dar
S Darem s tím se nepodělím
We'll search the forests
Prohledáme lesy
we will search all the farms
Prohledáme všechny farmy
We'll go to the castle
Půjdeme do zámku
and to the Red Lantern
I do Červené Lucerny
We will spend hours
Strávíme hodiny
searching the whole town
Prohledáváním celého města
and If we'll have to
Jestli bude třeba
we will search even a monastery
Prohledáme dokonce klášter
Our stuff got stolen
Ukradli nám zboží
tell me, where Dar could have hid it.
Pověz mi, kde Dar ho schoval.
I am looking for a package
Hledám balík
a tiny one and square-shaped
takový malý, hranatý
Perhaps I can help
Možná vám pomůžu
if there's a reward in it for me.
Pokud je v tom pro mně odměna.
Leave me alone
Dej mi pokoj
I'm having a headache all day.
Od rána bolí mně hlava.
Our stuff got stolen
Ukradli nám zboží
tell me, where Dar could have hid it.
Pověz mi, kde Dar ho schoval.
I am looking for a package
Hledám balík
a tiny one and square-shaped
takový malý, hranatý
Even if I knew
I kdybych vědel
I wouldn't say a word
Neřeknu ani slovo
I haven't heard
Neslyšel jsem
any rumors about it.
Že by o tom někdo mluvil.
WHERE IS HE?!
Kde je?!
We've searched the whole farm
Prohledali jsme celou farmu
all the floors, every corridor
všechna patra, každou místnost
No one has seen the mercenary
Nikdo neviděl žoldáka
that have vanished with our package
Který s naším balíkem zmizel
We won't find anything here
Nic už tu nenajdeme
it is time to leave this place
čas opustit tyto oblasti
We must ask everyone
Musíme se poptat všech
Dar couldn't have left the island
Dar nemohl opustit ostrov
We'll search the forests
Prohledáme lesy
we will search all the farms
Prohledáme všechny farmy
We will go to the castle
Půjdeme do zámku
and to the Red Lantern
I do Červené Lucerny
We will spend hours
Strávíme hodiny
searching the whole town
Prohledáváním celého města
and If we'll have to
Jestli bude třeba
we will search even a monastery
Prohledáme dokonce klášter
Our stuff got stolen
Ukradli nám zboží
tell me where Dar could have hid it
Pověz mi, kde Dar ho schoval
I am looking for a package
Hledám balík
a tiny one and square-shaped
takový malý, hranatý
You were supposed to search for dragons
Měl si hledat draky
I don't know what you're still doing here
Nevím, k čemu je tento rozhovor
Don't disturb me
Nevyrušuj
I must observe the orcs
Musím skřety pozorovat
Our stuff got stolen
Ukradli nám zboží
tell me, where Dar could have hid it
Pověz mi, kde Dar ho schoval
I'm looking for a package
Hledám balík
a tiny one and square shaped.
takový malý, hranatý
Isn't it that package
Není to ten balík
you were supposed to confiscate
který jsi měl zkonfiskovat
Better tell me
Radši mi pověz
if you have seen my liver
Kde jsou moje játra
I'm almost certain, that it's here
Jsem si docela jistý, že sem
my senses lead me here
Mně vedou smylsy
a smell of swampweed can be felt
Zápach trávy z bažin jde cítit
somewhere in this area
v této části ostrova
You still have one place to check
Ještě musíte zkontrolovat jednu z cest
before the night will come
Než noc padne
If you'll head down the road
Když půjdete po téhle cestě
you will find the mercenary
Najdete žoldáka
What are you going to do about the thief, then?
Co tedy chceš s tím zlodějem udělat?
I'll catch him puffing away on my weed.
Nachytám ho, jak kouří mou trávu.
And then I'll find a quiet spot and teach him a lesson he won't forget.
A pak si najdu nějáké odlehlé místo a dám mu takovou lekci, na kterou do smrti nezapomene.
What do you mean?
To znamená?
It's quite simple!
No to je jednoduché!
I'LL FLATTEN HIM!
ROZMLÁTÍM MU HUBU!
Translation: Delph, GaroK
CZE translation by: Romanez
So I've got you after ALL!
A už mi neutečeš!